Okay, the reason why
I asked you guys out
to brunch today is
because I've been doing
some thinking
about who should be
my Maid of Honor.
Oh, my God,
this is it!
Oh!
I really hope it's you.
I hope it's you.
Me, too.
First of all, I love you both
so much
and you're both so important
to me...
Okay, blah-la-la-la.
Who is it?
Well, I was thinking that
maybe we could come up
with a system
where we trade off being
Maid of Honor for each other.
Like, hypothetically,
if Phoebe were mine...
Yes! Oh!
Hypothetically.
Still.
If Phoebe were my Maid of Honor,
Rachel would be Phoebe's.
I would be Rachel's.
That way we all get to do it
once and no one would get upset.
Uh-hmm. No, that's
actually a pretty good idea.
Yeah, I'll do that.
So, who gets to be yours?
Well, this is the best part.
You guys get to decide.
Why is that
the best part?
Because then I don't have to.
Well, of course
we will help you decide.
We will do anything
we can to help you.
Okay, now, I'd like
to make a toast:
To the future Mrs. Chandler Bing
my best friend
and truly one
of the nicest people that...
Really not deciding.
Fine!
Excuse me.
I couldn't help
overhearing.
You're marrying Chandler Bing?
Yeah, that's right.
Huh...
Good luck!
Oh, and good luck to you, too.
What a nice lady.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Both:
Yeah!
Woo-hoo!
Die Hard--
still great.
Yup.
Hey, what do you say
we make it a double feature?
What else
did you rent?
Die Hard II!
Joey, this is
Die Hard I again.
Oh...
Well, we watch it
a second time
and it's Die Hard II!
Joey, we just saw it.
And?
And it would be cool
to see it again. Yeah!
Both:
Die Hard!
Dude, you didn't say "Die Hard."
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I just got,
uh, I got plans.
Well, John McClain had plans.
No, you see, the thing is,
I want to get out of here
before Joey gets all worked up
and starts calling
everybody "bitch."
What are you talking
about, bitch?
Yeah?
Hey, Rachel.
When I get married,
will you be my Maid of Honor?
Really?
Oh, my God, Phoebe.
I mean, I'm just...
Wait a minute.
If I'm your
Maid of Honor
that means that
you are Monica's.
Oh...
Well, if that's what you want.
Oh!
No! Wait, Phoebe.
I want to be Monica's.
But why does it even matter?
Why does it matter
so much to you?
Because this one is now!
And, and it's two
of our best friends.
Who knows what
you're going to marry?
What, what if I marry Ross?
Or Joey?
( gasps )
You wouldn't.
Okay, look, Rachel
I know you really want
to do this
but I've never been
Maid of Honor
to anyone before
and I know you've done it
at least twice.
Yeah, but, Phoebe...
Please, oh, please,
let me finish.
Oh, I guess that was it.
Okay.
Okay, since you've
never done it before
you can be
Monica's Maid of Honor.
Oh, thank you so much!
Yay.
( sighs )
I'm going to marry
someone good, you know.
Oh, I know.
Better than Chandler.
( scoffs )
( both scream )
What happened?!
I don't know.
We fell asleep, that is all.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right.
Well, uh, I better go.
Yeah, I think
that would be best.
Yeah, all right.
I'll talk to you later.
Okay.
But not about this.
No, never!
Never!
So, uh...
Bye.
No touch! No touch!
No.
Hey, you know, a weird thing
happened today
when I was at brunch.
This woman overheard that
I was marrying you
and she wished me
good luck.
That's sweet.
No, it was more
like a "good luck!"
So, uh, what did
this woman look like?
She was, like, 30,
dark hair, attractive.
Well, is there any chance
you were looking
into a bright, shiny thing
called a mirror?
Come on.
Was it someone
you dated in college?
No, no, I only dated two girls
in college
both blonde,
both not attractive...
Hold on one second.
Let me check this out.
What are you doing?
Well, let's see.
Okay, uh, is that her?
Oh, my God, yes!
Who is she?
Julie Graff,
my camp girlfriend.
Did you break up with her?
No, we're still together.
( chuckles )
Yeah, we went out
for two summers
and then I broke
up with her.
Why?
Well, because she came
back the third summer
and she had gotten
really fa...aaaa...aaaa...
Fat?
I did not say fat.
I said fa...aaaa...aaaa...
You broke up with a girl
because she was fat?
Yeah, yeah, but it was
a really, really
long time ago.
Does she still feel bad?
Apparently, she does.
Well, you know what they say,
elephants never forget.
Seriously,
good luck marrying me.
Hey, what's going on?
Hey, Phoebe is going to be
Monica's Maid of Honor.
Hey, well I hope
it goes better
than the last time
you did it
for that girl
downstairs, remember?
What? Hey!
You have been
Maid of Honor before?
You see, this is exactly why
you shouldn't lie.
All right, that's it.
I am Maid of Honor.
No, I am!
How come you are?
Because I cared
enough to lie.
Hey, hey, hey.
I can help
you decide who
should do it.
Yeah, we could have,
like, an audition
and see how you'd handle
Maid-of-Honor-type situations.
What are you talking about?
Like when I want a job,
I go to an audition.
And if I'm the best
of the people they see
they give me the part.
Okay, so after
this audition
who decides
who gets it?
Oh, uh, me and Ross
could be the judges.
Well, it's better
than us deciding.
Oh, come on, this is crazy.
Can't we just flip a coin?
No, coins hate me.
Okay, fine.
You know what?
We will let Ross
and Joey decide.
All right.
( seductively ):
Hi, Ross
sweetie.
Hey, there, handsome thing.
Wow, this cologne really is
every bit as good as Georgio.
Hey.
Just, uh, brought back
your videos.
Hey, uh, Ross, look, uh, I think
we need to talk about before.
No. No, we don't.
Yes, we do.
Now, look
that was the best nap
I ever had!
I don't, I don't know what
you're talking about.
Come on. Admit it.
That was the best nap
you ever had!
I've had better.
Okay. When?
All right, all right!
It was the best nap ever!
Uh-huh.
I said it, okay!
But it's over, Joey!
I want to do it again.
We can't do it again.
Why not?
Because it's weird!
Fine.
You want something to drink?
Sure, what do you got?
Warm milk and Excedrin P.M.
Chandler.
Chandler, I just figured out
who you are.
Can you figure out
what I'm doing?
You're Louis Posin.
Who?
Louis Posin. He was
my best friend in fifth grade
and then one day I asked him
to be my boyfriend
and he said no.
Do you know why?
Because you kept talking
to him
while he was trying
to go to the bathroom?
No, but because he thought I was
too "fa...aaaa..."
And every time
I think about it
it makes me feel as bad
as I did in fifth grade.
You know, I really
think that you should
apologize to Julie.
Honey, are you kidding?
That was, like,
16 years ago.
I know, but, you
know, it would make
me feel better
if Louis apologized to me.
Okay, I will do it,
but I have to warn you
this may make me a better
person, and that is not the man
you fell in love with.
All right, this is how
it's going to work.
We're going to give you
hypothetical Maid of
Honor situations
and you'll be scored
on a scale of one to ten
one being the highest.
No, ten is the highest.
Why is ten the highest?
Because it's the highest.
Okay, Rachel
you're up first.
Situation #1.
You're with Monica.
The wedding is
about to start
when Monica gets
cold feet. Go!
I don't want
to marry Chandler!
Okay, um...
I've got
cold feet.
It's going
to be okay.
One man the rest
of my life?
I don't know
if I can do it.
This means I'll
never get to sleep
with Joey!
Look, Monica,
getting cold feet is
very common, you know?
It's just because
of all the anticipation.
And you just have to remember
that you love Chandler.
And also, I ran out
on a wedding.
You don't get
to keep the gifts.
Very good.
Drawing on your
own experience.
Thanks, cool.
Okay, good.
Yes, very nice, Rachel.
Thank you, judges.
Oh, kiss ass.
Uh!
Okay, Phoebe.
Yes, Your Honor.
We're now in
the ceremony.
Monica is about
to say "I do"
when her drunk uncle
starts yelling.
What do you do? Go!
When Monica was a little girl
I remember that...
( yells )
Oh!
Ow!
Very good!
Yes, excellent.
Perfect score.
Wait a minute.
She just made
a scene
in the middle
of the ceremony.
Hey, you want
a little taste of Pheebs?
It is time for you
to give your Maid
of Honor speech.
Oh, wait a minute,
we haven't even prepa...
Go!
Okay, okay, um...
Webster's dictionary defines
marriage as a...
No, no, forget that!
That sucks!
Okay, never mind. Forget it.
Um, um, okay.
Uh, I met Monica when we were
just a couple of six-year-olds
and, uh, became friends
with Chandler when he was 25...
although he seemed
like a six-year-old.
Oh, that was nice.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Um, I've known them separately
and I've known them together
and to know them as a couple is
to know that you are
truly in the presence of love.
So, I would like to raise
my glass to Monica and Chandler
and the beautiful adventure
they are about to embark upon
together.
I can think of no two people
better prepared for the journey.
Wow.
Great speech.
Yeah, it really was.
Oh, thanks.
Okay, Phoebe,
I guess you're next...
although I really
don't see the point.
Yeah.
Okay.
( clears throat )
I can't believe that
Monica and Chandler are
getting married.
I remember talking about this
day with Rachel
while we were showering
together... naked.
And she's back
in the game!
Julie, hi.
Chandler Bing.
I, uh, guess you
remember me.
Hello, Skidmark.
It's a nickname.
I'll explain later.
It's pretty clear.
Uh, I owe you
a long-overdue apology.
I never should've
broken up with you
because you were
overweight.
That's why you broke up with me?
Y-y-you didn't know that?
Well, I guess
my work here is done.
Well, first of all,
I would like to say
that you both performed
very well, okay?
You should be proud
of yourselves.
And I'd also like
to say
that in this competition,
there are no losers...
Well, except Rachel...
Damn it!
Really? I won?
What?
I'm sorry, Rach.
It was
really close.
Well, then,
I demand a recount!
Actually it wasn't
that close.
No! You know what?
No. Your thing was
so stupid anyway.
We're going to flip a coin.
( gasps )
All right? Heads.
Oh!
The coins have
finally forgiven me.
Well, you
know what?
I hope Monica forgives you
after you throw her
her vegetarian, voodoo,
goddess-circle-y shower.
Rach, it's going
to be okay.
You guys are the best.
Boy, I'll tell you
that judging stuff
took a lot out of me.
Yeah?
Yeah, I was thinking about maybe
going upstairs
and taking a little nap
on my couch...
Wh-why would I care about that?
No reason.
I'm just saying that, uh...
...that's where I'll be.
As bad as that went
I actually
enjoyed myself.
I think that I am going
to apologize for all
the stupid things that I do.
Why don't you just
stop doing stupid things?
Then you wouldn't
have to apologize.
I'd really love it
if I could do both.
All right, I have to ask...
What?
Are you going
to break up with me
if I get fat again?
What?
You broke up with
Julie Graff.
How much weight
could she have gained?
145 pounds.
In one year?
My God, what did she
eat, her family?
That's not the point.
Look, I know it was
a stupid reason
to break up with somebody,
but I was 15.
That's not the only time
this was an issue.
You remember when you spent
Thanksgiving with us?
You called me fat.
Okay, okay, now, wait a minute.
That was totally different.
How?
You were not supposed
to hear that.
I said that behind your back.
What if I have babies, okay?
I mean, I'm going
to look different.
I'm okay with that,
but I'm not sure
that you are.
You have to realize
I don't think of you
as a thin, beautiful woman.
See, this is one of the things
that I can apologize for later.
What I mean is,
you're Monica, okay
and I am in love with Monica.
Keep going.
So you can balloon up
or you can shrink down
and I will still love you.
Even if I shrink down
to two inches tall?
I'd carry you around
in my pocket.
I love you.
Skidmark's still got
a way with the ladies.
Hi, Pheebs.
Hi.
I just want
to apologize.
I'm really sorry
I was a baby.
That's ridiculous, Rachel.
We were all babies once.
Oh, you mean today.
Yeah, and you know,
you deserve to win.
And, you know, I was
thinking about it--
if you're Monica's
Maid of Honor
that means that
I get to be yours.
Oh, yeah!
Yeah.
Oh, um, when Monica
and Chandler got engaged
I started putting some
stuff together
you know, just in case.
Oh, that's so sweet. Thanks.
Here is a book of poetry
that I know Monica loves.
And, uh, oh, God
this is funny.
Look, here's a picture
from one Halloween
where she dressed up
as a bride.
And look, she made me
carry her train
which was weird, because
I was Wonder Woman.
Oh, and here's
a little purse
that I found.
You know, I just thought
they could maybe hold
the rings in there.
Oh, yeah.
And, um,
here are some
vintage handkerchiefs,
you know
because people cry
at weddings.
( voice breaking ):
I'm just going to grab
a couple of these.
This stuff is great.
Oh, I forgot this
was in here.
Um, this was the garter
that I was saving
for my wedding...
And I wanted it to be Monica's
something borrowed...
And it's blue...
You know, Rach, I think
that you should be
Monica's Maid of Honor.
You do?
Why?
Because I think it
means more to you.
But Pheebs, you know,
you earned it.
It's fine.
I mean, this is
something
that you've been
thinking about
since you were, what, 14?
No, I was ten.
I just developed early.
Man alive!
Hey, what's going on?
Hey!
Well, we just decided
that Rachel
is going to be
your Maid of Honor.
Oh, that's great!
Oh, wow, okay, we really
have to start planning.
I have a lot of really
specific ideas.
We should probably
get together, like,
four times a week.
You can come over
to my place.
We'll get together
before work...
What do you say,
6:30, my place?
So excited!
Yeah, okay, you laugh now...
She's going to be yours.
( sniffing )
Mm, great nap.
It really was.
( clears throat )
Dude, what the hell
are you doing?!
God...!
Excuse me.